<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Adrian L Thomas]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pizza, programming and cars - sometimes in that order.]]></description><link>https://www.adrian-thomas.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 20:07:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[The Beginning]]></title><description><![CDATA[Well, it’s been nearly 5 years since I last wrote any kind of personal blog. I’ve written several posts for employers (a few pieces on…]]></description><link>https://www.adrian-thomas.com/blog/2021-09-06/the-beginning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.adrian-thomas.com/blog/2021-09-06/the-beginning/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Well, it’s been nearly &lt;a href=&quot;https://adrianlucathomas.blogspot.com/&quot;&gt;5 years&lt;/a&gt; since I last wrote any kind of personal blog. I’ve written several posts for employers (a few pieces on NodeJS, Golang, GitHub Actions, etc.), but I finally got my act together and put something under my own domain. I’ve been writing lots of React lately, and also Gatsby in my own time - so it felt like a good idea to start off with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://gatsbystarterblogsource.gatsbyjs.io/&quot;&gt;Gatsby Starter Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I introduced &lt;a href=&quot;https://styled-components.com/&quot;&gt;styled-components&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://eslint.org/&quot;&gt;ESLint&lt;/a&gt; and put something basic together (that I plan to improve over time).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m going to use this platform for trying out some new tooling (maybe take a look at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/AdrianLThomas/AdrianLThomas.github.io/issues&quot;&gt;issues here&lt;/a&gt; for a sneek peak), but I’ll also write about my hobbies (see the header!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, because I’m a proper Yorkshireman - this blog runs on &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt; for free, with the DNS &amp;#x26; CDN managed at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudflare.com/&quot;&gt;Cloudflare&lt;/a&gt; for free. I build this blog on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/features/actions&quot;&gt;GitHub Actions&lt;/a&gt; for… free. I suppose I do pay a few quid a year for the domain…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s all for now!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>